[
  {
    "question": "The books .... on the table in the living room",
    "options": [
      "is",
      "are",
      "Functionâ€¦",
      "----"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "are"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't have .... money for lunch",
    "options": [
      "some",
      "few",
      "any",
      "little"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "any"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have .... friends in America",
    "options": [
      "little",
      "few",
      "a little",
      "a few"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a few"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are .... students",
    "options": [
      "a lot of",
      "much",
      "any",
      "---"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "a lot of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you know .... who has got blue hair?",
    "options": [
      "somebody",
      "someone",
      "anybody",
      "something"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "anybody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Linkin Park was a very popular band. .... knows it.",
    "options": [
      "Everyone",
      "They",
      "Someone",
      "anybody"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Everyone"
  },
  {
    "question": "I .... studied Chinese for five years.",
    "options": [
      "having",
      "has",
      "have",
      "had"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "have"
  },
  {
    "question": "We'll find a hotel .... we arrive in Jakarta",
    "options": [
      "when",
      "while",
      "until",
      "what"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "When we arrive in Los Angeles we'll need to rest, because we .... about 800 miles.",
    "options": [
      "will be driving",
      "will have driven",
      "will drive",
      "will"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "will be driving"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa and I .... sick yesterday.",
    "options": [
      "am",
      "are",
      "were",
      "is"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "were"
  }
]